I thought you would be able to go, so you will see how I have it down there.
Against Afghanistan.
Sometimes you come down as a foreign soldier and want to change the world
During the small six months.
But there is very little you can do during that time.
Still, you are a cog to get something in the right direction, hopefully.
I think it feels like we made a difference when we were there.
The impression you got from the locals and those we talked to
When one made things that got a concrete difference
So it felt like one created security
And made it better for the population, they contributed to a development in the right direction.
Then they experienced that it became
a clearly more strained position
and more sharp tasks
to try to influence what happened
More than just watching, observing, as you may have done before.
Preferably one was in southern Afghanistan
at the larger conflicts, at first
And then it also spread to northern Afghanistan.
It's been a tough night on the mountain top at the mast tonight
First we had a post at the top of the top
Then we were forced to regroup
Down to the Compo Round in the middle of the night.
We had to wake the Ana soldiers so they would not freeze to death.
Now we have camped here instead.
We came down on the FS20 in December.
We were a unit that would follow the Afghan Army
And be embedded in it, surrounded.
We didn't have much to do with the larger Swedish units.
For most of the mission.
To avoid carrying it.
They look exhausted and sweaty
While I was driving I tried to send out water bottles
Through the small grenade hatch found on the box.
Deport PET bottles so they could drink.
We tried to support them the best we could
And went through this mountain pass with 20-30 vehicles.
We made our way up to the village of Jarghan where we could collaborate with the population.
Half town is here and welcomes us.
Here is the village where we have our location
Where we opened our base.
It looks like an old cowboy constellation
Where you put the tensions in ring.
The village is called Jarghan.
Here next to Ana lives in a compound.
They are building a building, a school maybe.
If they had managed fully -skinned
Or if something had happened you might have missed.
Someone who had been injured or so.
But once we arrived and could talk to each other
saw that everyone was full -skinned
So it became a pretty excited atmosphere.
That everything had gone well, you were very relieved.
One was not satisfied and happy that
It had become a dangerous situation or that you have been shot.
That everyone managed was nice.
One was somehow prepared to